Interviewer: Hannah works for the BBC.
She has a son Kit who’s three years old.
Hannah, what time do you usually get up?
Hannah: I get up at 7.00. But I also get up in the night, because Kit usually calls me.
I tell him to sleep, but he usually comes into my bed.
Interviewer: Do you usually feel tired?
Hannah: Yes, I always feel tired!
Interviewer: Do you have a shower or a bath in the morning?
Hannah: I turn on the TV for Kit and then I have a bath in five minutes.
Interviewer: Do you always have breakfast?
Hannah: Yes, I need breakfast every day!
Interviewer: Where do you have it?
Hannah: I have it in a café on the way to work.
Interviewer: What do you have for breakfast?
Hannah: I have a coffee and sometimes I have some toast with avocado.
It’s delicious.
Interviewer: What time do you go to work?
Hannah: The perfect time to leave the house is at 8.00,
but we usually leave at twenty past eight.
Interviewer: Do you usually need to hurry in the morning?
Hannah: Yes, always!
Interviewer: Do you like mornings?
Hannah: Yes. I love mornings.
Interviewer: Why?
Hannah: Because I love my job, and I’m happy to go to work!